(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T22:45:10.040310",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
常闇トワ JACK!
[Tokoyami Towa JACK!]
あ、こっちこっち！
Ah, over here, over here!
今日2人じゃないんすね
Wait, it's not just the two of us today?
え？2人？
Huh? Two of us?
さっきの…ここで会った人たち！
Those people from earlier... that we met here!
え？
Huh?
心で…
With my heart...
Joyにしてこうぜ！
Let's Joy it up!
JOYSOUND X1
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon...
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ：演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください。声出し応援OKです。
Notice to Attendees: Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance. Cheering loudly is OK.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[The concert will be starting soon]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: Notice to Attendees]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
Attention: Notice to Attendees
見える？この目の涙 命の色に滲んでいる
Can you see it? The tears in my eyes are blurring into the color of life.
何を残して与えた？ 問いかけて潰れて
What did I leave behind to give? Asking that, I break down...
青と赤と白混ざる この世の中で叫んでいる
Shouting in this world where blue, red, and white blend together.
何を求めて歩いた？ 追いかけて疲れて
What did I walk seeking? I'm exhausted from chasing after it.
どのくらい異常？
How broken am I?
壊れているの？ 壊れているよ
Am I broken? Yes, I am broken.
それでも息を…したい したい
Even so, I want to... breathe, I want to breathe.
君に見えてるの？ 夢のように
Can you see it? Like a dream...
最後の言葉も詰まるよ ERROR
My final words get stuck too, error.
遠い日のこと 淡い光が空に溢れている
A distant day... a faint light overflows across the sky.
何を選んで並べた？ 涙色重ねて
What did I choose to line up? Layering the colors of my tears.
浮かぶその身体 意識の中溶けて滲んでしまう
My floating body melts into consciousness and bleeds through.
何を見てきて比べた？ 悲しくて忘れて
What did I look at and compare? It's so sad, so I forgot.
どのくらい異常？
How distorted am I?
歪んでいるの？ 歪んでいるよ
Am I distorted? Yes, I am distorted.
それでも息を…したい したい
Even so, I want to... breathe, I want to breathe.
夢を見ているの 想う君に
I'm dreaming of you, whom I hold dear...
最後の言葉も詰まるよ ERROR
My final words get stuck too, error.
与えることも 失うことも
I can neither give nor lose,
忘れることも できないの
nor can I forget.
あふれだすこのエラー
This overflowing error...
壊して笑う僕がまた
I, who break down and laugh, am once again...
壊しているの
...breaking down.
壊して知るの
Through destruction, I learn.
それでも涙 痛い 痛い
Even so, the tears pain me, pain me so.
君に届いたの
Did it reach you?
歌は声に 最後の
The song turns into a voice,
言葉並べても
even as I line up my final words.
重ならない色に滲んで
Blurring into unharmonious colors,
壊れていくの
I am breaking apart.
I am falling apart.
それでも息を したい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to breathe.
君に見えてたの
Could you see it?
夢のように 最後の
Like a dream,
言葉も詰まるよ
even my last words choke up.
ERROR
乾いた
Dried up...
虚しさと
...emptiness,
小さな この騒音を 抱えて
and this small noise I hold within...
痛かった
It hurt...
彼方の色
The distant colors...
手を伸ばすほどに 遠く
The further I reach my hand out, the further away they get.
僕たちは何度も
Over and over again,
何度も問いかけて
over and over again, we question it.
灯火は 迷子を照らすかな
Will this light illuminate those who are lost?
まだ世界は 無答の時間のまま
The world remains in a time without answers,
やがて消えていくの
fading away eventually.
静かな
Quietly...
暗闇と
...darkness,
確かな 感覚を
and a certain sensation...
君の中の正義が 愛がこぼれ落ちたら
If the justice and love inside you were to spill over,
すべて試されてみても いいの
would it be okay even if everything were tested?
抱いていたもの
The things I held close,
何度も失って
lost time after time.
この日々が 夢であるなら
If these days are but a dream...
まだここからは 目を閉じたまま
...then from here on, with eyes still closed,
やがて消えて 崩れていく
eventually fading away and collapsing...
やめてよ
Stop it...
増える感情
...these multiplying emotions.
苦しくて
It hurts so much...
僕たちは あやまちの中で
Inside of our mistakes,
何度も試されて
tested again and again,
まだ正義や 愛とか 有限の
is this world of finite justice and love...
この世界は 目を閉じたまま
...still closing its eyes?
やがて消えて 崩れていく
Eventually fading away and collapsing...
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind,
誰にも気づかれぬよう
so that no one will notice...
区別がつかない モノクロの世界
Indistinguishable, in a monochrome world.
何も見えなくて
I couldn't see anything,
まるで私は
as if I had...
息を止めていた
stopped breathing altogether.
眩しいよ 遠くても
It's so bright, even from afar,
叶えたい 私は
I want to fulfill it,
声なき世界
in a voice-less world.
思いも 抱きしめていたつのに
I wanted to hold onto my feelings, and yet...
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
打ち続ける意味は
what is the meaning of continuing to strike it?
この胸に 輝いている
Shining within this chest of mine...
ストーリー
is my story.
応えることに 意味などないけど
There's no meaning in answering, but...
拾い集めた 欠片
these pieces I gathered...
失うの？
will I lose them?
そして 夜は
And so, the night...
その冷たさを
melts away that coldness...
溶かして 手を伸ばした
as I reached out my hand.
眩しいよ 遠くても
It's so bright, even from afar,
届けたい 私は
I want it to reach you.
受け止めてく
I'll accept them all,
涙も 抱きしめていたいのに
even these tears I wish to embrace, and yet...
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
心込めるのは
pouring my heart into it...
この空に
Into this sky,
描き出し続けてゆく
I continue to depict...
ストーリー
my story.
そして 夜は
And so, the night...
その冷たさを
melts away that coldness...
溶かして 手を伸ばした
as I reached out my hand.
眩しいよ 遠くても
It's so bright, even from afar,
叶えたい 私の
I want to fulfill it.
声なき世界
My voice-less world,
言葉で包むんだ
I will wrap my feelings in words.
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of dreams,
色を足していく
adding colors one by one...
この胸に
Within this chest,
今輝いて
now shining bright...
強くなくてもいい
It's fine even if I'm not strong,
壊れかけてもいい
it's fine even if I'm breaking down.
この心は
This heart of mine...
永遠にはばたいて
will flutter away into eternity.
響く夜に
Into the echoing night,
塗り替えてゆく
repainting it anew...
パレット
Palette.
皆！
Everyone!
常闇トワです！
I'm Tokoyami Towa!
あ、声返してくれるんだ！
Ah, you're cheering back!
常闇トワ 2nd Solo Live "Shout out"!
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Solo Live "Shout out"!
いよいよ始まりましたー！
Has finally begun!
えー、ちょっとびっくりすると思うんですけども
Um, I think you might be a bit surprised,
最初に「ERROR」を歌わせていただきました！
but first off, I sang "ERROR"!
びっくりした人ー？
Who here was surprised?
そうだよね、そうだよね。びっくりしますよね。
Right, right. It is surprising, isn't it?
ね、その後に「Twilight」と「Palette」を歌わせていただきました。
And after that, I sang "Twilight" and "Palette".
えー、やっぱりね、「ERROR」を持ってきた理由なんですけれども
Um, as for the reason why I brought "ERROR" here...
やっぱりね、まあ「ERROR」を聞いて常闇トワのことを知ってくれたみたいな人がやっぱり
Because many people came to know Tokoyami Towa after listening to "ERROR"...
多いと思うんだよね。
I think there are a lot of people like that.
そうだよね？
Right?
多いから、なんかちょっとエモいの持ってこようかなーみたいな
Since there are many, I thought, "Maybe I should bring out something emotional!"
感じで、もうそんな感じで、ころっと、さらっと決めちゃいました！
And just like that, I decided on it pretty easily and casually!
なんか結構最初のほうにこう、しっとりする曲を持ってきたのは
Bringing out such mellow songs right at the beginning...
結構挑戦的だったのかなと思うんですけども
was probably quite a challenge, I think.
どうでした？
How was it?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
えー、みんなTシャツ着てくれてるやん！
Eh, everyone's wearing the T-shirts!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ペンライトはね、あの、鈍器にもなりかねないので気をつけてください！
Be careful with those penlights, as they could practically turn into blunt weapons!
いや可愛いんだけど、可愛いのにね！
I mean, they're cute, even though they're cute!
前のはちょっとあの 尖りすぎたっていう
"The last one was a bit too edgy," or something.
まあ、それもありますけども、思い出として残しておいてください。
Well, there was that too, but please keep it as a memory.
はい！
Alright!
え、そしてね、今回
And also, this time...
えー、ライブなんですけれども
um, regarding this concert...
セカンドアルバムが、えー、「SINK」というアルバムになっていまして
the 2nd album is titled "SINK,"...
ま、ライブもね、その「SINK」に沿って、えー、「SHYNER」という風につけさせていただいております！
and following "SINK", we named this live "SHYNER"...
あの、歌はいいけど喋りが下手っていう、致命的に下手なんだけど大丈夫そうか？
You know, "great singing but bad at talking"... I'm fatally bad at it, but are you guys doing okay?
あ、ありがとうございます、ありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you so much, thank you!
えー、このね、「SHYNER」はね、えー、光るとか輝くっていう意味があるので
Um, "SHYNER" means to light up or shine, so...
今日のね、ライブは来てくれてるみんなの心を輝かせるようなライブにして行きたいと思っております！
for today's concert, I want to make it shine in the hearts of everyone who came!
えー、セカンドアルバムのね、楽曲もいっぱいあるので、楽しみにしていてください！
Um, there are lots of songs from the 2nd album, so please look forward to it!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
アルバムも買ってくれましたか？
Did you all buy the album as well?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
嬉しいです。なんか今日もちょっとライブ前に、あの、エゴサをしてたんですけども
I'm so happy. Today before the concert, I was vanity searching online...
あの、いっぱい現地でも買いましたみたいなポスト、ポストカード？ゲットしました！みたいな
and saw lots of posts saying "I bought it at the venue!" or "I got the postcard!"
ポストしてるのを見て、あ、ポストしてるのを見て、すごい嬉しかったです。
Seeing those posts made me really happy.
まだ慣れないんだよねー。
I'm still not used to saying "post"!
えー、そして、え、今日なんですけれども、ファーストと一緒で生バンドでやっております！
And today, just like the 1st concert, we're performing with a live band!
イエーイ！かっこよかったでしょ？
Yay! Weren't they super cool?
もう最初だけじゃないから、これからずっとかっこいいの演奏してくれます！
It's not just the intro, they'll be playing awesome music the whole time!
よろしくお願いいたします！
Please give them a big round of applause!
え、今日しか、なんと今日しか聴けないライブアレンジがあったりするので、楽しんで盛り上がってくれたら嬉しいです！
There are special live arrangements you can only hear today, so I hope you get hyped and enjoy!
はい！
Yeah!
そして、今日は現地だけじゃなくて配信もしております！
And today, we're not only here live, but also livestreaming!
なんと、ここら辺に手を振ると、可愛いトワちゃんが、あの、インターネットを通じて…
And if I wave my hand around here, a cute Towa-chan will, via the internet...
あ、ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you so much! Thank you!
はいはい、ちょっとあんまりそんな、あの、言われ慣れてないもんで。はい。
Yeah, yeah, I'm not really used to being praised like that, so... yeah.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
えー、なんか色んなところにアピールしながらやっていこうかなと思っております！
Um, I'm going to perform while sending love to everyone everywhere!
え、そして今回の
And for this concert's...
ハッシュタグなんですけれども、ライブの感想ハッシュタグ、#常闇トワ2nd でたくさんポストしていってください！
hashtag, please post lots of your concert thoughts using #常闇トワ2nd!
スクリーンショットOKってことなので、いっぱい、あの、盛れてる感じのでお願いいたします！スクショとして投稿する場合は。
Screenshots are allowed, so if you post any, please pick cute and flattering ones!
はい、お願いいたします！
Yes, please do!
そして、なんと…
And, surprisingly...
これいつも流れだから分かっちゃうかもしれないけど…
You might already know because it's the usual flow, but...
そうなんです！YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでとなっております！
That's right! For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is where the free stream ends!
すみません！
Sorry!
えー！お前ら「えー」じゃないだろ！
"Ehh?!" Don't you guys in the audience go "Ehh?!"!
いるだろ！何が「えー」なんだよ！何に対しての「えー」なんだよ！
You're here live! Why are you saying "Ehh"?! What is that "Ehh" for?!
ね、配信を見てくれてる人の「えー」って言う…
Oh, you're saying "Ehh" on behalf of the stream viewers...
代弁してくれたってことね？
Speaking for them, right?
そうだよね、そうだよね。
I see, I see!
はい！なのでね、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄から配信サイトをチェックして購入してくださいね！
So if you want to keep having fun with us, check the stream link in the description box and buy a ticket!
はい！
Alright!
ということで、次の曲に行こうかなと思うんですけども
So with that, I'd like to move on to the next song, but...
まずちょっとアンケートを取りたいと思います！
first I'd like to take a quick audience survey!
本日、東京から来たよって方ー！
Is there anyone here who came from Tokyo today?!
半分くらいかな？半分くらい？
About half of you? About half?
じゃあ、東京じゃないところから来た人ー！
Then, who came from outside Tokyo?!
むっちゃくちゃ多いやん！めっちゃありがとやん！
That's so many of you! Thank you so much!
じゃあ、じゃあ北海道から来た人ー！
Then, then... who came from Hokkaido?!
いるやん！マジかよ！ありがとう！
You're here! Seriously?! Thank you!
じゃあ沖縄から来た人ー！
Then, who came from Okinawa?!
お、いるいるいるいる！ありがとう、ありがとう！
Oh, there are some! Thank you, thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい！じゃあ、ちょっともっと拡大していいですか？
Alright! Can I expand the scale even further?
日本じゃないところから来た人ー！
Who came from outside Japan?!
おいおい、めちゃめちゃいるじゃないか！おお、すごいすごい！ありがとう！
Woah woah, there are so many of you! Oh, amazing, amazing! Thank you!
じゃあ、さらにめちゃくちゃ絞って…
Now then, narrowing it down even further...
12時間以上乗ってきた人？
Anyone who traveled for more than 12 hours to get here?
え？あ、いるやん！
What? Ah, there are people!
え、すご...
Wow, incredible...
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you!
ということで...なんか「わー」って今言えました？
So... were you able to cheer just now?
あ、まだでも足りないか。
Ah, but maybe that's still not enough.
じゃあトワが掛け声言っちゃおうかな？
Then maybe Towa should do a hype call?
盛り上がれますかー？！
Are you ready to get hyped up?!
結構最初なのに声出てるやん！
Your voices are so loud even though it's just the start!
なんか何回かやろうかなって思ってたけど、結構声出てたけど...
I was thinking of doing it a few times, but you were already so loud...
ちょ、もう1回言っていい？じゃあ。
Wait, can I say it one more time then?
盛り上がれますかーー！
Are you ready to get hyped up?!
じゃあ！
Alright then!
次の曲行くぞーー！
Let's move on to the next song!
リベリオン！
Rebellion!
いくぞ、有明ーー！
Let's go, Ariake!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
The free preview has ended. Thank you for watching!